

14333 Van Nuys Blvd. Unit #73 Arleta, Ca 91331 (213)448-7523 Tai.Mujarin@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/taimujarin/ https://github.com/AyoTai

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Nursing.

Highly experienced in customer relation and knowledgeable in the hospitality field. Able to adapt to a variety of assignments and adhere to Company policy and procedure. Open to building new skill sets and challenges given.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL

Tools: Express, React, Node.js, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap

Experience

Nov 2014 - Oct 2019

Coremark Inc., Los Angeles, Ca - Merchandiser

- Daily commute to multiple brick and mortar storefronts to oversee quality and quantity of products and QC pricing to meet Coremark standards
- Maintain highest level of customer service with Clients
- Responsible for stocking, pricing, rotation of products
- Due-diligence in reviewing expired items and interchanging items with credit to Clients to avoid health and hazard issues for Consumers.
- Manage ordering products and replenishing products and ensuring there is sufficient stock.
- Create and deliver invoices to Coremark without mishaps and errors

Jul 2012 - Jun 2014

Meadowbrook of Agoura Hills Senior Living, Agoura Hills, Ca - Medical Technician

- Promoted to Medical Technician within 2 years
- Able to administer daily medication to the Elderly and supervise intake of required medications
- Perform daily vital signs and continue to monitor and complete intake report for Patients
- Review and recommend reports to Nurses, Supervisors, and upper management on daily conditions of Elders

 Close interaction with Patients and provide unconditional respect and understanding for the Elders

Jun 2010 - Jun 2012

Meadowbrook of Agoura Hills Senior Living, Agoura Hills, Ca - Caregiver

- Provide nurturing care and comfort to Seniors with daily living assistance
- Duties include bathing, toileting, dressing, grooming, feeding
- Assigned to Dementia Ward
- Assist LVN and RN with daily job functions and provide condition report to management
- Communicate and entertain Seniors with games, conversations, and other stimulating activities to help with Dementia
- Assist LVN and RN with intakes and reporting

Feb 2008 - May 2010

Kikka Sushi - Sushi Chef

- Trained and certified with Whole Foods hot food service
- Culinary expertise in Japanese food preparation
- Experience in creating and preparing sushi on a daily rotation
- Able to customize Sushi orders and develop new selection for management
- Successfully provide 5-star services for customers

EDUCATION

May 2021 - Jul 2021

UCLA Extension, Los Angeles, Ca -Full Stack Certificate

Jan 2011 - Feb 2012

Casa Loma Nursing College, Van Nuys, Ca - Associate Degree

August 12, 2010

Abraham Friedman Occupational CENTER, Los Angeles, Ca -

High School Equivalency Certificate

- Excellent communication skills and self-discipline
- Able to adapt to any environment
- Team leadership and provide peer support
- Certified Nurse Assistant
- Possess self-perseverance and flexible